krave.biz 2013-04-25

# Krave TE Social Community - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to the KRAVE Admin, as is your trust in KRAVE services. krave does not divulge or sell your information to any 3rd party unless under legal order to do so. This privacy policy outlines how your information is processed and used here.

Information Collection

During the contact process, Krave requires customers to supply necessary information such as their names, emails, etc. Every visitor to our website(s) is tracked for statistic purposes and data such as IP address, browser version, screen resolution and ISP hostname is collected. This information is used for analysis of webstats and is never made available to anyone outside the team in any way, shape or form. IP logging also enables KRAVE to handle abuse such as spamming or service rule violations. All comments posted on the site are IP logged for abuse protection.

There might be some chance for you to publish more personal information while you intend to interact with other users on KRAVE website(s) (e.g. writing a comment), blogs, articles, etc. by choosing to publish this personal information, you understand and agree that anyone may access and forward any information about you that is contained in or what you posted to those areas, and KRAVE is not to be held responsible for such released information.

Public Profile

A profile is one of the most important parts of the KRAVE experience, thus by default, your profile information along with (including, but not limited to) graphics, company name, domain name and comments, and interactions will be displayed on the website without any delays. In many cases you will not have the opportunity to delete it once it is posted. Other information such as your email address, etc, are for internal records only and will never be shared outside the team unless under legal order to do so.

Cookies

When you use some online services of KRAVE, a cookie text file may be stored on your local computer for sessions only. This enables you to remain logged in while using the services. KRAVE does not track your browsing habits with its cookies.

Cookies are small files which many websites transfer to your hard disk. They can inform the website what pages you visit, and your preferences, which enable websites to provide you with a more personalized service and experience. You may set your browser to refuse cookies, or to warn you before accepting them.

Outside Links

Our website(s) may contain links to third-party websites not controlled by KRAVE or covered by this Privacy Policy. It is recommended that you check the privacy statement of other websites you visit before providing any personal information, and we are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

Disclaimers

This website contains general information that is intended, but not guaranteed, to be correct, complete, up-to-date or error free. KRAVE uses reasonable precautions to keep all personal information provided secure. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security which is out of our control or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.

Payments

KRAVE does not store credit card details in any way, shape or form. All customers are advised to check the website of our payment processors and read their privacy policy and terms and conditions.

Changes To Privacy Policy

KRAVE reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time we see fit and without notice.

Privacy Inquiries

Please feel free to contact us for any further information or questions about this page.

Last updated: May 9, 2011 (EST)
